<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://aidenhuynh.github.io/CS_Swag/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://aidenhuynh.github.io/CS_Swag/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-09-06T16:54:15-05:00</updated><id>https://aidenhuynh.github.io/CS_Swag/feed.xml</id><title type="html">coolest blog EVER?! (clickbait)</title><subtitle>flashfweqofj[spkjsa;lkfe;fdnoeqrghf;sgisglknv;grt3]</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Loops, Dictionaries, and Lists</title><link href="https://aidenhuynh.github.io/CS_Swag/jupyter/markdown/2022/09/05/dictionaries-test.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Loops, Dictionaries, and Lists" /><published>2022-09-05T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2022-09-05T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://aidenhuynh.github.io/CS_Swag/jupyter/markdown/2022/09/05/dictionaries-test</id><author><name></name></author><category term="jupyter" /><category term="markdown" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Testing out different loops in combination with lists and dictionaries]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Week 2 - Data Abstraction &amp;amp; HTML Fragments</title><link href="https://aidenhuynh.github.io/CS_Swag/markdown/2022/09/05/Week_2_Review_Ticket.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Week 2 - Data Abstraction &amp;amp; HTML Fragments" /><published>2022-09-05T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2022-09-05T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://aidenhuynh.github.io/CS_Swag/markdown/2022/09/05/Week_2_Review_Ticket</id><author><name></name></author><category term="markdown" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[hacks for week 2]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Psychology Ch 9 Corrections</title><link href="https://aidenhuynh.github.io/CS_Swag/2022/09/04/Psychology-Ch-9-Corrections.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Psychology Ch 9 Corrections" /><published>2022-09-04T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2022-09-04T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://aidenhuynh.github.io/CS_Swag/2022/09/04/Psychology-Ch-9-Corrections</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Q # Question &amp; Analysis Why? E X A M P L E Question: What did Lev Vygotsky state about children’s learning? Correct Answer (write it out, not just the letter!): Social contact is essential to intellectual development Why the correct answer is right (content based explanation): Vygotsky’s theory about the zone of proximal development indicates that children learn from mentors or coaches. Why your answer was wrong (re-word the q to make your wrong ans right): Q: What did Albert Bandura suggest about the way children learn? A: He said that children learn through observational learning, or imitation. If your wrong answer cannot be made correct, just explain: Children learn by imitating others was my incorrect choice, but Vygotsky is not the one who says this, this is more along the lines of what Albert Bandura’s theories suggest. Textbook page you referenced for your explanation: Chapter 1 Sec 2 (pg. 15) Choose one: Didn’t study Read question wrong Absent when taught Never understood concept Other (specify) Question: Which of the following techniques used by professional therapists are highly likely to promote the construction of false memories? Correct Answer (write it out, not just the letter!): Hypnosis, imagination-enhancing techniques, and drug-induced recall. Why the correct answer is right (content based explanation): All of these techniques can implant false memories. Those with vivid imaginations were found to be more susceptible to “imagination inflation,” where repeatedly imagining nonexistent events creates false memories. Therefore, enhancing imagination would increase the amount of false memories. Drug-induced recall and hypnosis have been criticized heavily by psychologists, to the point of being agreed upon as unreliable by several large organizations. Why your answer was wrong (re-word the q to make your wrong ans right): What psychotherapy practice(?) used by professional therapists are highly likely to promote the construction of false memories? If your wrong answer cannot be made correct, just explain: Textbook page you referenced for your explanation: 383, 388 Choose one: Didn’t study Read question wrong Absent when taught Never understood concept Other (Answer said “all of the above, but only two were above so I just chose one”)]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Basic Python Quiz</title><link href="https://aidenhuynh.github.io/CS_Swag/jupyter/markdown/2022/09/04/Python_Quiz.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Basic Python Quiz" /><published>2022-09-04T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2022-09-04T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://aidenhuynh.github.io/CS_Swag/jupyter/markdown/2022/09/04/Python_Quiz</id><author><name></name></author><category term="jupyter" /><category term="markdown" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Includes different messages based on final percentage]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Week 1 - Intro to Python, Bash, and Fastpages Frontend Development</title><link href="https://aidenhuynh.github.io/CS_Swag/markdown/2022/09/04/Week_1_Hacks.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Week 1 - Intro to Python, Bash, and Fastpages Frontend Development" /><published>2022-09-04T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2022-09-04T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://aidenhuynh.github.io/CS_Swag/markdown/2022/09/04/Week_1_Hacks</id><author><name></name></author><category term="markdown" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[submissions for week 1]]></summary></entry></feed>